Hello!
I'm Naki Inoue from Nogizaka46.
We are in
in Singapore.
We are shooting a music video for “Cheat Day”.
We are here in Singapore to shoot the music video for “Cheat Day”.
We are going to start filming here now.
We are going to start filming in Singapore.
Here we go.
What do you think?
It's amazing!
Great, great, great.
Singapore.
Aya's going to fall.
Oh, my God, guys!
They're getting closer, they're getting closer.
What's this?
Aya's going to slip on the beach.
When she falls down...
Everyone rushed to the beach
The DJ booth is now empty...
Nagi...
“jacking” the DJ booth...
I'm trying to get a picture of that.
Guide way on!
I'm coming!
D joint
DJ!
Cool DJ!
Cлонl original
Just a little hug!
You're too good to me.
What? Because...
There's a lot of echo code. There are so many ecodes.
Oh, I just noticed.
I'll take it.
Hey, guys, give me a ride around here, will you?
Okay.
Put on some music.
Play something.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What are you doing?
Music
music
I'm taking live pictures now.
I'm taking pictures.
I'm glad.
I'm sitting next.
Yes, sir.
Oh, they're letting him through.
Ladies and gentlemen.
We're putting the two cameras together.
Okay, I'm on it.
Thank you very much.
Singapore Special.
Just do a little practice.
OK, wihast start
See you in the next video.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, Saidi Bite Guys.
Camera's rolling.
Okay, let's go.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Come on, let's go.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay. Okay. Yes, okay.
See you later.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Yes, OK.
How was the sorry scene?
Sorry scene? I can't wait to see how it turns out.
Let's talk about yesterday.
I'll ask you to tell us about yesterday's sorry scene.
We had to meet yesterday morning.
I got on the bus right on time.
But on the way there, I realized I didn't have my passport.
I rushed home to get it, but I couldn't find it.
I called a lot of people.
I called a lot of people and apologized to them.
In the end, I called my friend.
I called my friends, and they asked me what's in the box over there. And...
All kinds of things.
You found a friend?
I couldn't find anything on my own.
I thought I'd call someone who knows us.
I just saw a friend at the top of the list.
So I called my friend.
I found him.
Good night.
Good night, ma'am.
Score of 100.
That was a hell of a way to put it.
Somebody's car fight.
He's lying.
Don't let your head hit the floor.
That's cute.
Oh, my God.
He's so cute.
I'm scared. Scary.
Oh, my God.
You guys look like you're getting along great.
Have a good day.
Japanese guy.
Japanese man
fast forward
It's the morning of the second day.
Yes, it is!
It's just like the locals!
It's an amazing city!
The one we went to yesterday is totally different from the one we went to yesterday...
It's so strong!
Wow!
This is so fun!
Looks delicious!
I like Kami
I like Kami.
No, Kami's on top!
Kami stood on top.
I like Kami better
Tastes like this
This one.
Cute.
Here.
Don't take it if it's in there.
Oh, I think that's it.
Let's go home.
I'll be back in an hour.
I'm so happy.
I was happy. Thank you. I was happy. Thank you.
I'm safe and praying for you.
LOL!
LOL.
That's special, right?
LOL!
Potatoes and irises.
Very hot!
My friend took a picture of me and episdea
I love it!
Seira Liro
This is magnificent!
thank you so much!
The face never changes.
I'm so happy
New employee
I love it
I'm done
Oh, I'm sorry
Sorry, sorry
I'm the girl who cruises everything.
Thank you.
Dr. Kelo, I'm motivated.
Don't do it.
Crush me.
I'm not crushing it.
I'm not breaking it.
I'll do it.
This is the long ring.
Here.
What's the next course? What's the next course?
What's the next course?
Next course?
The next cut is the last one.
Oh, my God.
That's a great final scene.
Such a cute place to shoot.
This is probably Sacchan's house.
It's light blue and pink.
Aya's house.
White
Light blue and pink.
Their bicycles are cute!
So cute!
It's the last one.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, let's go with him.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, so...
We just finished shooting the music video for “Tweet Day.
That was fun.
It was hot.
Everyone was sweating
Thank you for your hard work!
Lastly, we wore school uniforms.
We're all looking forward to seeing you in uniform.
Hey, guys!
There's an “N” in the name
N for Ayaka
N for...
N for Nagi.
Sorry, I was a little overconfident.
No, it's not.
It was a lot of fun, and we had a great time in Singapore. We had a great time in Singapore.
And the music video shoot is over, so have fun.
I'm sure it's going to be a great music video.
I can't wait to see it!
I hope you'll watch it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
It was the best number sheet day of the summer!
Well, it was an unexpected request.
Yes, I know.
It's nice, isn't it?
Summer hands!
I'm feeling summer.
I feel like dancing.
Let's dance together
Hey...
I'm sure they'll dance for you.
People who are listening to the dance
“Oh, my God!” they'd say.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
OK.
They were laughing a little.
Oh, no, no, no!
One more time.
the end